

Lesya Stulkivska



Junior FrontEnd Developer

https://legrito.github.io/resume/



Horishni Plavni, Poltava region, Ukraine

Professional Summary

Solution-driven, high-motivated Front End Developer ready to become a part of the team and work for a common result. Would like to grow up and pump professional skills on real projects. My goal is to become a Middle Front End Developer in two years.

Phone

+38097-994-77-86

Email

jamma@i.ua





Work History

2013-07 -Current

Manager

Sewing manufacture, Horishni Plavni, Poltava region

- Ensured new material shipments at different stages of manufacturing to align with procurement expectations.
- Managed production schedules and arranged timely delivery according to orders.
- Arranged for proper storage and inventory of products.
- Implemented stock inventory software.
- Developed an online store on Tilda.

HTML5

CSS3/SASS

JAVASCRIPT/ES6

REACT

REDUX

REST API

WEBPACK

WEDITIER

GIT/GITHUB
PHOTOSHOP

FIGMA

2011-10 -2013-06

Typesetter

Newspaper "TE", Horoshni Plavni, Poltava region

- Prepared visual and textual materials for production.
- Utilized different technologies, including Adobe InDesign, Adobe Illustrator and Adobe Photoshop, to ready artwork for offset printing purposes.
- Generated prepress proofs in digital or other formats to approximate appearance of final printed piece.
- Worked collectively with various partners such as designer, editor, journalist and management team to reach deadlines and meet customer expectations.



Education

2006-09 -2011-06 Master of Science |
Computer Technologies of Publishing
Kharkiv National University of Radio Electronics

No Degree | Fullstack Development
GolT Online

2020-10 -Current Language

English - A2/B1